{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781241128","data":{"timestamp":" 946781241127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781256456","data":{"timestamp":" 946781256456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hik_"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781265708","data":{"timestamp":" 946781265708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tang_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781267548","data":{"timestamp":" 946781267548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_tang_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781274027","data":{"timestamp":" 946781274026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_tang_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-4.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781281294","data":{"timestamp":" 946781281293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_tang_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781289675","data":{"timestamp":" 946781289675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 513c4472-4d80-4bc1-81ac-807d16fca5a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_tang_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781302878","data":{"timestamp":" 946781302878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781303110","data":{"timestamp":" 946781303110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781303554","data":{"timestamp":" 946781303554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781303988","data":{"timestamp":" 946781303988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781304302","data":{"timestamp":" 946781304302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781305110","data":{"timestamp":" 946781305109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781305714","data":{"timestamp":" 946781305714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781305969","data":{"timestamp":" 946781305968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781306763","data":{"timestamp":" 946781306763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781309565","data":{"timestamp":" 946781309564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781311375","data":{"timestamp":" 946781311375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781313705","data":{"timestamp":" 946781313705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781315356","data":{"timestamp":" 946781315355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781317393","data":{"timestamp":" 946781317393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781319619","data":{"timestamp":" 946781319619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781321937","data":{"timestamp":" 946781321937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781324581","data":{"timestamp":" 946781324581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781326704","data":{"timestamp":" 946781326704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781328780","data":{"timestamp":" 946781328779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781329768","data":{"timestamp":" 946781329768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781330214","data":{"timestamp":" 946781330213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781330404","data":{"timestamp":" 946781330403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781331011","data":{"timestamp":" 946781331010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781334139","data":{"timestamp":" 946781334138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781335950","data":{"timestamp":" 946781335950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781337678","data":{"timestamp":" 946781337678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781339335","data":{"timestamp":" 946781339335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781339607","data":{"timestamp":" 946781339607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781341955","data":{"timestamp":" 946781341955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781342593","data":{"timestamp":" 946781342592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781343360","data":{"timestamp":" 946781343360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781346193","data":{"timestamp":" 946781346193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781348279","data":{"timestamp":" 946781348279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781350129","data":{"timestamp":" 946781350129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781352323","data":{"timestamp":" 946781352323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781352985","data":{"timestamp":" 946781352985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781353839","data":{"timestamp":" 946781353839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781354062","data":{"timestamp":" 946781354062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781354816","data":{"timestamp":" 946781354816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781355670","data":{"timestamp":" 946781355670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781356752","data":{"timestamp":" 946781356752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781357766","data":{"timestamp":" 946781357766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781358680","data":{"timestamp":" 946781358680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781359743","data":{"timestamp":" 946781359743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781360157","data":{"timestamp":" 946781360157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781360760","data":{"timestamp":" 946781360760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781360933","data":{"timestamp":" 946781360933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781361506","data":{"timestamp":" 946781361506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781365659","data":{"timestamp":" 946781365658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781367216","data":{"timestamp":" 946781367216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781374141","data":{"timestamp":" 946781374141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781375919","data":{"timestamp":" 946781375918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781378754","data":{"timestamp":" 946781378753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781380729","data":{"timestamp":" 946781380729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781382632","data":{"timestamp":" 946781382632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781385394","data":{"timestamp":" 946781385394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781386968","data":{"timestamp":" 946781386968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781390364","data":{"timestamp":" 946781390364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781392370","data":{"timestamp":" 946781392370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781409707","data":{"timestamp":" 946781409706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781412617","data":{"timestamp":" 946781412616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781427291","data":{"timestamp":" 946781427290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781429870","data":{"timestamp":" 946781429869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781431039","data":{"timestamp":" 946781431038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781431763","data":{"timestamp":" 946781431762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781435476","data":{"timestamp":" 946781435476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781437588","data":{"timestamp":" 946781437588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781439947","data":{"timestamp":" 946781439947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781442568","data":{"timestamp":" 946781442568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781443203","data":{"timestamp":" 946781443198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781443638","data":{"timestamp":" 946781443637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781444153","data":{"timestamp":" 946781444152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781444646","data":{"timestamp":" 946781444646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781444872","data":{"timestamp":" 946781444871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781445580","data":{"timestamp":" 946781445579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781453241","data":{"timestamp":" 946781453241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781457170","data":{"timestamp":" 946781457169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781459783","data":{"timestamp":" 946781459783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781462325","data":{"timestamp":" 946781462325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781465393","data":{"timestamp":" 946781465393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781467985","data":{"timestamp":" 946781467985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781468465","data":{"timestamp":" 946781468465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781470572","data":{"timestamp":" 946781470571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781471165","data":{"timestamp":" 946781471164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781471698","data":{"timestamp":" 946781471698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781472161","data":{"timestamp":" 946781472160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781475898","data":{"timestamp":" 946781475897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781478907","data":{"timestamp":" 946781478906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781480925","data":{"timestamp":" 946781480925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781483953","data":{"timestamp":" 946781483953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781486288","data":{"timestamp":" 946781486287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781487052","data":{"timestamp":" 946781487052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781487985","data":{"timestamp":" 946781487985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781489328","data":{"timestamp":" 946781489328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781489982","data":{"timestamp":" 946781489982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781490344","data":{"timestamp":" 946781490344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781490877","data":{"timestamp":" 946781490876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781491949","data":{"timestamp":" 946781491949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781493042","data":{"timestamp":" 946781493042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" KUMUAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781496638","data":{"timestamp":" 946781496638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781500961","data":{"timestamp":" 946781500961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781508310","data":{"timestamp":" 946781508310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781524647","data":{"timestamp":" 946781524647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781527044","data":{"timestamp":" 946781527044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781528954","data":{"timestamp":" 946781528954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781531015","data":{"timestamp":" 946781531015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781533602","data":{"timestamp":" 946781533602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781536318","data":{"timestamp":" 946781536317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781538708","data":{"timestamp":" 946781538707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781538921","data":{"timestamp":" 946781538921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781539304","data":{"timestamp":" 946781539303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781539807","data":{"timestamp":" 946781539806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781541015","data":{"timestamp":" 946781541014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781541891","data":{"timestamp":" 946781541891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781542924","data":{"timestamp":" 946781542924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781543558","data":{"timestamp":" 946781543558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781543811","data":{"timestamp":" 946781543811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781544396","data":{"timestamp":" 946781544395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781551349","data":{"timestamp":" 946781551349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781553257","data":{"timestamp":" 946781553257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781555285","data":{"timestamp":" 946781555285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781557048","data":{"timestamp":" 946781557047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781559188","data":{"timestamp":" 946781559188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781560952","data":{"timestamp":" 946781560951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781563062","data":{"timestamp":" 946781563062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781565150","data":{"timestamp":" 946781565150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781566977","data":{"timestamp":" 946781566977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781569342","data":{"timestamp":" 946781569342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781571813","data":{"timestamp":" 946781571813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781572166","data":{"timestamp":" 946781572166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781572630","data":{"timestamp":" 946781572629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781573192","data":{"timestamp":" 946781573192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781573386","data":{"timestamp":" 946781573386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781573969","data":{"timestamp":" 946781573969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781582502","data":{"timestamp":" 946781582502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781589511","data":{"timestamp":" 946781589510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781591455","data":{"timestamp":" 946781591455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781593090","data":{"timestamp":" 946781593090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781595570","data":{"timestamp":" 946781595570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781595846","data":{"timestamp":" 946781595846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781597518","data":{"timestamp":" 946781597518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781597961","data":{"timestamp":" 946781597961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781599174","data":{"timestamp":" 946781599173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAIKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781601937","data":{"timestamp":" 946781601937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781607088","data":{"timestamp":" 946781607088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781609880","data":{"timestamp":" 946781609880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781612101","data":{"timestamp":" 946781612101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781612765","data":{"timestamp":" 946781612765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781613568","data":{"timestamp":" 946781613568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781614031","data":{"timestamp":" 946781614031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781614475","data":{"timestamp":" 946781614475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781614967","data":{"timestamp":" 946781614967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781624815","data":{"timestamp":" 946781624815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781627207","data":{"timestamp":" 946781627206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781629596","data":{"timestamp":" 946781629596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781631207","data":{"timestamp":" 946781631206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781633198","data":{"timestamp":" 946781633197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781635333","data":{"timestamp":" 946781635333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781638131","data":{"timestamp":" 946781638131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALAMIKA"," userResponse":" WALILALAMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781638646","data":{"timestamp":" 946781638646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781639250","data":{"timestamp":" 946781639250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781640337","data":{"timestamp":" 946781640337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHELEWA"," userResponse":" ILICHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781644189","data":{"timestamp":" 946781644189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALAMIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781645917","data":{"timestamp":" 946781645917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781647968","data":{"timestamp":" 946781647968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781650250","data":{"timestamp":" 946781650249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHELEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781651994","data":{"timestamp":" 946781651994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781653301","data":{"timestamp":" 946781653300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMETUACHA"," userResponse":" IMETUACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781657059","data":{"timestamp":" 946781657059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781658986","data":{"timestamp":" 946781658986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMETUACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781661191","data":{"timestamp":" 946781661190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781662269","data":{"timestamp":" 946781662268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781662554","data":{"timestamp":" 946781662553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781663818","data":{"timestamp":" 946781663818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781666823","data":{"timestamp":" 946781666823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781670073","data":{"timestamp":" 946781670073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781671755","data":{"timestamp":" 946781671754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781673850","data":{"timestamp":" 946781673850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781676268","data":{"timestamp":" 946781676268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTAWEZA"," userResponse":" HATUTAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781676892","data":{"timestamp":" 946781676891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781677824","data":{"timestamp":" 946781677823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781681516","data":{"timestamp":" 946781681515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781683261","data":{"timestamp":" 946781683261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781685007","data":{"timestamp":" 946781685006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781687204","data":{"timestamp":" 946781687204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAPATA"," userResponse":" SITAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781687538","data":{"timestamp":" 946781687538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781688071","data":{"timestamp":" 946781688071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781688158","data":{"timestamp":" 946781688158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781688835","data":{"timestamp":" 946781688835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781690111","data":{"timestamp":" 946781690110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781693288","data":{"timestamp":" 946781693288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781695902","data":{"timestamp":" 946781695902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781697979","data":{"timestamp":" 946781697979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781699628","data":{"timestamp":" 946781699628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781701390","data":{"timestamp":" 946781701390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781705410","data":{"timestamp":" 946781705409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781708371","data":{"timestamp":" 946781708371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781708517","data":{"timestamp":" 946781708517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781709073","data":{"timestamp":" 946781709072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781710042","data":{"timestamp":" 946781710042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATA"," userResponse":" WALIKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781710846","data":{"timestamp":" 946781710845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781711651","data":{"timestamp":" 946781711651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUDI"," userResponse":" WAKARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781712504","data":{"timestamp":" 946781712504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781715801","data":{"timestamp":" 946781715800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781717400","data":{"timestamp":" 946781717400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781719635","data":{"timestamp":" 946781719634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781721700","data":{"timestamp":" 946781721699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781723662","data":{"timestamp":" 946781723662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781726043","data":{"timestamp":" 946781726043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781728719","data":{"timestamp":" 946781728719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781730789","data":{"timestamp":" 946781730788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781731416","data":{"timestamp":" 946781731416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781732398","data":{"timestamp":" 946781732397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781733881","data":{"timestamp":" 946781733881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKATAA"," userResponse":" AKAKATAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781734625","data":{"timestamp":" 946781734624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781737283","data":{"timestamp":" 946781737282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781739592","data":{"timestamp":" 946781739591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781743308","data":{"timestamp":" 946781743307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781745707","data":{"timestamp":" 946781745706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKATAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781747538","data":{"timestamp":" 946781747538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781749210","data":{"timestamp":" 946781749210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781749756","data":{"timestamp":" 946781749756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781751254","data":{"timestamp":" 946781751254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781752892","data":{"timestamp":" 946781752892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUTASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781753929","data":{"timestamp":" 946781753929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781756637","data":{"timestamp":" 946781756637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781758636","data":{"timestamp":" 946781758636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781762000","data":{"timestamp":" 946781762000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781765258","data":{"timestamp":" 946781765258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781767511","data":{"timestamp":" 946781767510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781770185","data":{"timestamp":" 946781770184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781771568","data":{"timestamp":" 946781771568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" WALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781772391","data":{"timestamp":" 946781772390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781775182","data":{"timestamp":" 946781775181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781777757","data":{"timestamp":" 946781777757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781780179","data":{"timestamp":" 946781780178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781782168","data":{"timestamp":" 946781782168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781782782","data":{"timestamp":" 946781782782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUMBI"," userResponse":" VUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781783546","data":{"timestamp":" 946781783545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781786507","data":{"timestamp":" 946781786507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781788443","data":{"timestamp":" 946781788442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUMBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781790235","data":{"timestamp":" 946781790235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781792013","data":{"timestamp":" 946781792013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781792654","data":{"timestamp":" 946781792654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781793532","data":{"timestamp":" 946781793532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781796542","data":{"timestamp":" 946781796542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781800121","data":{"timestamp":" 946781800121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781803278","data":{"timestamp":" 946781803278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781805966","data":{"timestamp":" 946781805965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781806473","data":{"timestamp":" 946781806472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781807143","data":{"timestamp":" 946781807142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781807574","data":{"timestamp":" 946781807573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781814341","data":{"timestamp":" 946781814341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781816694","data":{"timestamp":" 946781816694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781819417","data":{"timestamp":" 946781819417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781820384","data":{"timestamp":" 946781820384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781822796","data":{"timestamp":" 946781822796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781823429","data":{"timestamp":" 946781823429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781827986","data":{"timestamp":" 946781827986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781829798","data":{"timestamp":" 946781829798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781831566","data":{"timestamp":" 946781831566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781831989","data":{"timestamp":" 946781831989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781832762","data":{"timestamp":" 946781832762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781833705","data":{"timestamp":" 946781833705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781834098","data":{"timestamp":" 946781834098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781834761","data":{"timestamp":" 946781834761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781838249","data":{"timestamp":" 946781838249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781840835","data":{"timestamp":" 946781840835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781843113","data":{"timestamp":" 946781843113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781845093","data":{"timestamp":" 946781845093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781847583","data":{"timestamp":" 946781847583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781849390","data":{"timestamp":" 946781849390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781852228","data":{"timestamp":" 946781852227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALIOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781854532","data":{"timestamp":" 946781854531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WALIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781857357","data":{"timestamp":" 946781857357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781860651","data":{"timestamp":" 946781860651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781863376","data":{"timestamp":" 946781863376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUINGIA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781863918","data":{"timestamp":" 946781863917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781867960","data":{"timestamp":" 946781867960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781870305","data":{"timestamp":" 946781870304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781872731","data":{"timestamp":" 946781872730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781873714","data":{"timestamp":" 946781873714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" ALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781878839","data":{"timestamp":" 946781878838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781881316","data":{"timestamp":" 946781881315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781883587","data":{"timestamp":" 946781883586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" TUMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781884051","data":{"timestamp":" 946781884050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781884914","data":{"timestamp":" 946781884913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781885913","data":{"timestamp":" 946781885912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781889443","data":{"timestamp":" 946781889443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781891379","data":{"timestamp":" 946781891379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781894185","data":{"timestamp":" 946781894184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781896817","data":{"timestamp":" 946781896817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781899491","data":{"timestamp":" 946781899491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781899655","data":{"timestamp":" 946781899655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781900036","data":{"timestamp":" 946781900036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781900538","data":{"timestamp":" 946781900538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781901233","data":{"timestamp":" 946781901232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781901428","data":{"timestamp":" 946781901428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781901938","data":{"timestamp":" 946781901937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781902696","data":{"timestamp":" 946781902696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781908909","data":{"timestamp":" 946781908908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781911478","data":{"timestamp":" 946781911478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781913314","data":{"timestamp":" 946781913314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781915319","data":{"timestamp":" 946781915319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781917514","data":{"timestamp":" 946781917514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781919558","data":{"timestamp":" 946781919557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781921083","data":{"timestamp":" 946781921083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781923568","data":{"timestamp":" 946781923568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781925272","data":{"timestamp":" 946781925272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781925746","data":{"timestamp":" 946781925746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781926450","data":{"timestamp":" 946781926450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781927434","data":{"timestamp":" 946781927433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781927988","data":{"timestamp":" 946781927988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781928050","data":{"timestamp":" 946781928050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781928623","data":{"timestamp":" 946781928623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781928962","data":{"timestamp":" 946781928962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781929442","data":{"timestamp":" 946781929441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781930195","data":{"timestamp":" 946781930195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781932868","data":{"timestamp":" 946781932868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781934341","data":{"timestamp":" 946781934341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781936236","data":{"timestamp":" 946781936235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781938672","data":{"timestamp":" 946781938671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781940905","data":{"timestamp":" 946781940904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781943343","data":{"timestamp":" 946781943343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781945464","data":{"timestamp":" 946781945464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781947554","data":{"timestamp":" 946781947554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781949211","data":{"timestamp":" 946781949211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781951318","data":{"timestamp":" 946781951318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781953699","data":{"timestamp":" 946781953698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781954513","data":{"timestamp":" 946781954512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781955717","data":{"timestamp":" 946781955716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781959895","data":{"timestamp":" 946781959894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781963844","data":{"timestamp":" 946781963844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781967164","data":{"timestamp":" 946781967164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781969254","data":{"timestamp":" 946781969254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781969716","data":{"timestamp":" 946781969715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781970391","data":{"timestamp":" 946781970390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781971098","data":{"timestamp":" 946781971097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781971954","data":{"timestamp":" 946781971953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781972524","data":{"timestamp":" 946781972524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781972700","data":{"timestamp":" 946781972700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781973299","data":{"timestamp":" 946781973298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781976209","data":{"timestamp":" 946781976208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781978048","data":{"timestamp":" 946781978047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781979968","data":{"timestamp":" 946781979967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781981942","data":{"timestamp":" 946781981942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781984466","data":{"timestamp":" 946781984466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781986372","data":{"timestamp":" 946781986372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781988062","data":{"timestamp":" 946781988061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781990142","data":{"timestamp":" 946781990142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781992532","data":{"timestamp":" 946781992531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781993106","data":{"timestamp":" 946781993106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781993852","data":{"timestamp":" 946781993852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781995265","data":{"timestamp":" 946781995265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" WALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781996342","data":{"timestamp":" 946781996341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIFIKIA"," userResponse":" KUIFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781997040","data":{"timestamp":" 946781997039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781999849","data":{"timestamp":" 946781999848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782002787","data":{"timestamp":" 946782002786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782004980","data":{"timestamp":" 946782004980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782008940","data":{"timestamp":" 946782008940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782011150","data":{"timestamp":" 946782011150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIFIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782014233","data":{"timestamp":" 946782014232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782016214","data":{"timestamp":" 946782016214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782017090","data":{"timestamp":" 946782017089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782018157","data":{"timestamp":" 946782018156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782021773","data":{"timestamp":" 946782021773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782024276","data":{"timestamp":" 946782024276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782027384","data":{"timestamp":" 946782027384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782029195","data":{"timestamp":" 946782029195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782030263","data":{"timestamp":" 946782030262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ILIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782030786","data":{"timestamp":" 946782030786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782031679","data":{"timestamp":" 946782031679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782035270","data":{"timestamp":" 946782035270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782037820","data":{"timestamp":" 946782037820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782040281","data":{"timestamp":" 946782040281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782042152","data":{"timestamp":" 946782042151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782044396","data":{"timestamp":" 946782044395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782044849","data":{"timestamp":" 946782044849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782045362","data":{"timestamp":" 946782045362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782045616","data":{"timestamp":" 946782045616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782046538","data":{"timestamp":" 946782046538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782049587","data":{"timestamp":" 946782049586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782051627","data":{"timestamp":" 946782051626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782053358","data":{"timestamp":" 946782053358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782054894","data":{"timestamp":" 946782054894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782055354","data":{"timestamp":" 946782055354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782056985","data":{"timestamp":" 946782056985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782057439","data":{"timestamp":" 946782057439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782058063","data":{"timestamp":" 946782058063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782058938","data":{"timestamp":" 946782058937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782063984","data":{"timestamp":" 946782063984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782066172","data":{"timestamp":" 946782066172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782069976","data":{"timestamp":" 946782069976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782073605","data":{"timestamp":" 946782073605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782076280","data":{"timestamp":" 946782076279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIHARIBIKA"," userResponse":" ILIHARIBIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782077053","data":{"timestamp":" 946782077053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782078117","data":{"timestamp":" 946782078116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782081843","data":{"timestamp":" 946782081843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIHARIBIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782083680","data":{"timestamp":" 946782083679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782087583","data":{"timestamp":" 946782087582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782089518","data":{"timestamp":" 946782089518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782090508","data":{"timestamp":" 946782090508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUJA"," userResponse":" ITAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782091751","data":{"timestamp":" 946782091751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONGEZA"," userResponse":" ALIONGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782094548","data":{"timestamp":" 946782094548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782097012","data":{"timestamp":" 946782097012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782101145","data":{"timestamp":" 946782101145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONGEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782103412","data":{"timestamp":" 946782103412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782104466","data":{"timestamp":" 946782104466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782104930","data":{"timestamp":" 946782104929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782105055","data":{"timestamp":" 946782105055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782105873","data":{"timestamp":" 946782105872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782109495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782109494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782112036","data":{"timestamp":" 946782112036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782113993","data":{"timestamp":" 946782113993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782115685","data":{"timestamp":" 946782115684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782118009","data":{"timestamp":" 946782118009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782120090","data":{"timestamp":" 946782120090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782120811","data":{"timestamp":" 946782120811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUBWA"," userResponse":" UKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782121004","data":{"timestamp":" 946782121004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782121768","data":{"timestamp":" 946782121767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782125040","data":{"timestamp":" 946782125040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782127307","data":{"timestamp":" 946782127306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782129264","data":{"timestamp":" 946782129264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782131360","data":{"timestamp":" 946782131360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782134408","data":{"timestamp":" 946782134407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782135118","data":{"timestamp":" 946782135118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782135634","data":{"timestamp":" 946782135633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782136307","data":{"timestamp":" 946782136306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782137186","data":{"timestamp":" 946782137185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782137917","data":{"timestamp":" 946782137917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" INAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782138777","data":{"timestamp":" 946782138776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782141570","data":{"timestamp":" 946782141570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782144221","data":{"timestamp":" 946782144221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782146041","data":{"timestamp":" 946782146041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782148876","data":{"timestamp":" 946782148876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782151172","data":{"timestamp":" 946782151172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782154512","data":{"timestamp":" 946782154512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782157340","data":{"timestamp":" 946782157339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782159371","data":{"timestamp":" 946782159369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782159528","data":{"timestamp":" 946782159528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782167425","data":{"timestamp":" 946782167424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" ab99c81e-c58e-4af5-801f-a089fc097dda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782179364","data":{"timestamp":" 946782179363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_biye_biye-rutu-gove"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" biye"," userResponse":" biye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782187671","data":{"timestamp":" 946782187671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muye_muye-vifa-hejo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muye"," userResponse":" muye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782194485","data":{"timestamp":" 946782194485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tade_tade-zadi-lera"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tade"," userResponse":" tade"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782202703","data":{"timestamp":" 946782202703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bibo_pogu-wope-bibo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibo"," userResponse":" bibo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782209117","data":{"timestamp":" 946782209116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_yuka-zeti-goli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782215975","data":{"timestamp":" 946782215975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boyi_jara-boyi-topo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boyi"," userResponse":" boyi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782223357","data":{"timestamp":" 946782223357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_gove_gove-bobo-biye"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gove"," userResponse":" gove"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782232027","data":{"timestamp":" 946782232027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vifa_zadi-vifa-yuka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vifa"," userResponse":" vifa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782236978","data":{"timestamp":" 946782236978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sevu_sevu-vifa-fago"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sevu"," userResponse":" sevu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782241940","data":{"timestamp":" 946782241940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fago_fago-muma-gove"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fago"," userResponse":" fago"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782247678","data":{"timestamp":" 946782247677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fago_fago-muma-gove"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782294275","data":{"timestamp":" 946782294275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 5d996619-af76-418d-9fbe-df6c40e0d818"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fago_fago-muma-gove"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782308928","data":{"timestamp":" 946782308927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782309551","data":{"timestamp":" 946782309551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782309785","data":{"timestamp":" 946782309785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782310297","data":{"timestamp":" 946782310297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782311630","data":{"timestamp":" 946782311630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782311853","data":{"timestamp":" 946782311853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782312346","data":{"timestamp":" 946782312346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782313371","data":{"timestamp":" 946782313371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782314418","data":{"timestamp":" 946782314417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782315441","data":{"timestamp":" 946782315441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782318026","data":{"timestamp":" 946782318026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782318349","data":{"timestamp":" 946782318349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782318352","data":{"timestamp":" 946782318352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782326709","data":{"timestamp":" 946782326708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782328558","data":{"timestamp":" 946782328558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782330827","data":{"timestamp":" 946782330827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782332674","data":{"timestamp":" 946782332674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782338050","data":{"timestamp":" 946782338049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782340588","data":{"timestamp":" 946782340588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782342921","data":{"timestamp":" 946782342920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782345197","data":{"timestamp":" 946782345196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782347003","data":{"timestamp":" 946782347003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782348280","data":{"timestamp":" 946782348279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782348479","data":{"timestamp":" 946782348478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782349053","data":{"timestamp":" 946782349052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782351939","data":{"timestamp":" 946782351939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782354255","data":{"timestamp":" 946782354255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782356580","data":{"timestamp":" 946782356580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782358692","data":{"timestamp":" 946782358692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782361448","data":{"timestamp":" 946782361448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782362131","data":{"timestamp":" 946782362131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782363584","data":{"timestamp":" 946782363584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782364139","data":{"timestamp":" 946782364138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782364597","data":{"timestamp":" 946782364596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782365271","data":{"timestamp":" 946782365271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782365785","data":{"timestamp":" 946782365785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782366508","data":{"timestamp":" 946782366507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782366623","data":{"timestamp":" 946782366623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782367395","data":{"timestamp":" 946782367394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782369673","data":{"timestamp":" 946782369673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782371042","data":{"timestamp":" 946782371042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782371902","data":{"timestamp":" 946782371901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" START_AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782373592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782373591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782375928","data":{"timestamp":" 946782375928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782377991","data":{"timestamp":" 946782377991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782379202","data":{"timestamp":" 946782379201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782381025","data":{"timestamp":" 946782381025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782382900","data":{"timestamp":" 946782382900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782385077","data":{"timestamp":" 946782385077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782386603","data":{"timestamp":" 946782386603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782386890","data":{"timestamp":" 946782386890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782388593","data":{"timestamp":" 946782388593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782390098","data":{"timestamp":" 946782390098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782390605","data":{"timestamp":" 946782390605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782393345","data":{"timestamp":" 946782393345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782393988","data":{"timestamp":" 946782393988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782395083","data":{"timestamp":" 946782395083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782395728","data":{"timestamp":" 946782395727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782396573","data":{"timestamp":" 946782396572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782397098","data":{"timestamp":" 946782397097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782397707","data":{"timestamp":" 946782397706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782397885","data":{"timestamp":" 946782397884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782398562","data":{"timestamp":" 946782398561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782401103","data":{"timestamp":" 946782401102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" START_MAKUTANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782402120","data":{"timestamp":" 946782402120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782403792","data":{"timestamp":" 946782403792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782406651","data":{"timestamp":" 946782406650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782407783","data":{"timestamp":" 946782407783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782408742","data":{"timestamp":" 946782408742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782410464","data":{"timestamp":" 946782410464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782411914","data":{"timestamp":" 946782411913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782413528","data":{"timestamp":" 946782413528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782414837","data":{"timestamp":" 946782414837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782416116","data":{"timestamp":" 946782416116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782416512","data":{"timestamp":" 946782416512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782417061","data":{"timestamp":" 946782417060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" START_KUFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782420258","data":{"timestamp":" 946782420258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782422592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782422592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782422854","data":{"timestamp":" 946782422854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782423574","data":{"timestamp":" 946782423574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782427951","data":{"timestamp":" 946782427951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782428219","data":{"timestamp":" 946782428218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782430711","data":{"timestamp":" 946782430711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782432789","data":{"timestamp":" 946782432789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782435678","data":{"timestamp":" 946782435677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782436484","data":{"timestamp":" 946782436483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782437867","data":{"timestamp":" 946782437867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782438823","data":{"timestamp":" 946782438822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782439388","data":{"timestamp":" 946782439387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782440183","data":{"timestamp":" 946782440183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782440834","data":{"timestamp":" 946782440834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782443664","data":{"timestamp":" 946782443664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782445282","data":{"timestamp":" 946782445282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782447899","data":{"timestamp":" 946782447899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782449948","data":{"timestamp":" 946782449948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782451916","data":{"timestamp":" 946782451916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782454522","data":{"timestamp":" 946782454522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782456435","data":{"timestamp":" 946782456435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782458536","data":{"timestamp":" 946782458536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782459719","data":{"timestamp":" 946782459718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" MNGURUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782460375","data":{"timestamp":" 946782460374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782461666","data":{"timestamp":" 946782461666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" ULISIKIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782462181","data":{"timestamp":" 946782462181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782462854","data":{"timestamp":" 946782462853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782463359","data":{"timestamp":" 946782463358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782464141","data":{"timestamp":" 946782464140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782465004","data":{"timestamp":" 946782465004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782465268","data":{"timestamp":" 946782465268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782466307","data":{"timestamp":" 946782466306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782468908","data":{"timestamp":" 946782468907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782470879","data":{"timestamp":" 946782470879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782473352","data":{"timestamp":" 946782473352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782475688","data":{"timestamp":" 946782475688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782477555","data":{"timestamp":" 946782477555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782479503","data":{"timestamp":" 946782479503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782481718","data":{"timestamp":" 946782481718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782483641","data":{"timestamp":" 946782483641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782485799","data":{"timestamp":" 946782485799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782487434","data":{"timestamp":" 946782487434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782490714","data":{"timestamp":" 946782490713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782492949","data":{"timestamp":" 946782492948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782493502","data":{"timestamp":" 946782493501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782494636","data":{"timestamp":" 946782494636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782495120","data":{"timestamp":" 946782495120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782495262","data":{"timestamp":" 946782495262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782495807","data":{"timestamp":" 946782495806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782496340","data":{"timestamp":" 946782496340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782500310","data":{"timestamp":" 946782500310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782502364","data":{"timestamp":" 946782502363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782505811","data":{"timestamp":" 946782505810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782507650","data":{"timestamp":" 946782507649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782509544","data":{"timestamp":" 946782509542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782511681","data":{"timestamp":" 946782511681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782513785","data":{"timestamp":" 946782513785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782515819","data":{"timestamp":" 946782515818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782516666","data":{"timestamp":" 946782516665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" KUPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782517399","data":{"timestamp":" 946782517399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782524090","data":{"timestamp":" 946782524090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782527205","data":{"timestamp":" 946782527205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782529185","data":{"timestamp":" 946782529185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782531532","data":{"timestamp":" 946782531532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782532465","data":{"timestamp":" 946782532465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782533049","data":{"timestamp":" 946782533049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782533132","data":{"timestamp":" 946782533132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782533635","data":{"timestamp":" 946782533635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782534739","data":{"timestamp":" 946782534738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" AKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782535281","data":{"timestamp":" 946782535281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782537895","data":{"timestamp":" 946782537895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782540387","data":{"timestamp":" 946782540386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782542594","data":{"timestamp":" 946782542594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782544154","data":{"timestamp":" 946782544154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782546117","data":{"timestamp":" 946782546117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782548915","data":{"timestamp":" 946782548915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782551185","data":{"timestamp":" 946782551184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782552883","data":{"timestamp":" 946782552883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782553897","data":{"timestamp":" 946782553897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782554521","data":{"timestamp":" 946782554521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782555434","data":{"timestamp":" 946782555434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782556687","data":{"timestamp":" 946782556687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782557409","data":{"timestamp":" 946782557409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782558673","data":{"timestamp":" 946782558673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782561403","data":{"timestamp":" 946782561403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782564488","data":{"timestamp":" 946782564488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782566731","data":{"timestamp":" 946782566731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782568466","data":{"timestamp":" 946782568466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782570854","data":{"timestamp":" 946782570854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782574266","data":{"timestamp":" 946782574265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782576922","data":{"timestamp":" 946782576922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782579184","data":{"timestamp":" 946782579184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782579734","data":{"timestamp":" 946782579733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782580437","data":{"timestamp":" 946782580437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782581495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782581494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782581987","data":{"timestamp":" 946782581987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782583101","data":{"timestamp":" 946782583101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782584346","data":{"timestamp":" 946782584346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782587166","data":{"timestamp":" 946782587165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782589592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782589592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782592341","data":{"timestamp":" 946782592341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782594929","data":{"timestamp":" 946782594929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782597431","data":{"timestamp":" 946782597431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782599926","data":{"timestamp":" 946782599926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782602510","data":{"timestamp":" 946782602510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782604316","data":{"timestamp":" 946782604316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782605260","data":{"timestamp":" 946782605259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" AKAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782605725","data":{"timestamp":" 946782605725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782608445","data":{"timestamp":" 946782608445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782611237","data":{"timestamp":" 946782611237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782613231","data":{"timestamp":" 946782613231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782615377","data":{"timestamp":" 946782615377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHONI"," userResponse":" MWISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782616969","data":{"timestamp":" 946782616969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISINZIA"," userResponse":" ALISINZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782617218","data":{"timestamp":" 946782617217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782618100","data":{"timestamp":" 946782618100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782619503","data":{"timestamp":" 946782619502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782622872","data":{"timestamp":" 946782622872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782625099","data":{"timestamp":" 946782625099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISINZIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782626971","data":{"timestamp":" 946782626971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782629674","data":{"timestamp":" 946782629674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782632076","data":{"timestamp":" 946782632076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782634589","data":{"timestamp":" 946782634588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782635066","data":{"timestamp":" 946782635066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782636581","data":{"timestamp":" 946782636580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOROMOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782637102","data":{"timestamp":" 946782637102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782637495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782637495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782638079","data":{"timestamp":" 946782638079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782639303","data":{"timestamp":" 946782639303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782639706","data":{"timestamp":" 946782639706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782640169","data":{"timestamp":" 946782640169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782641133","data":{"timestamp":" 946782641132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" ALIYELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782644568","data":{"timestamp":" 946782644568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782646362","data":{"timestamp":" 946782646362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782648604","data":{"timestamp":" 946782648604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782651666","data":{"timestamp":" 946782651666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782654131","data":{"timestamp":" 946782654131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782656075","data":{"timestamp":" 946782656075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782658028","data":{"timestamp":" 946782658028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782660738","data":{"timestamp":" 946782660738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782663830","data":{"timestamp":" 946782663830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782666818","data":{"timestamp":" 946782666817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782669291","data":{"timestamp":" 946782669291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782670234","data":{"timestamp":" 946782670233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782670788","data":{"timestamp":" 946782670787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782672042","data":{"timestamp":" 946782672042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782672582","data":{"timestamp":" 946782672582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782673466","data":{"timestamp":" 946782673465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782676235","data":{"timestamp":" 946782676235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782678694","data":{"timestamp":" 946782678693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782681286","data":{"timestamp":" 946782681286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782683936","data":{"timestamp":" 946782683936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782685577","data":{"timestamp":" 946782685576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782688191","data":{"timestamp":" 946782688191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782690065","data":{"timestamp":" 946782690064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782691048","data":{"timestamp":" 946782691048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" ALISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782691492","data":{"timestamp":" 946782691492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782692005","data":{"timestamp":" 946782692005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782692618","data":{"timestamp":" 946782692618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782694288","data":{"timestamp":" 946782694288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782695336","data":{"timestamp":" 946782695336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" USALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782695761","data":{"timestamp":" 946782695761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782698594","data":{"timestamp":" 946782698593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782700701","data":{"timestamp":" 946782700700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782703525","data":{"timestamp":" 946782703525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782705222","data":{"timestamp":" 946782705222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782707064","data":{"timestamp":" 946782707064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782709335","data":{"timestamp":" 946782709334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782711262","data":{"timestamp":" 946782711262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782712856","data":{"timestamp":" 946782712856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782714899","data":{"timestamp":" 946782714899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782715511","data":{"timestamp":" 946782715510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782716605","data":{"timestamp":" 946782716604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782717572","data":{"timestamp":" 946782717572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782718567","data":{"timestamp":" 946782718567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" AKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782719107","data":{"timestamp":" 946782719107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782719620","data":{"timestamp":" 946782719620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782719792","data":{"timestamp":" 946782719792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782720335","data":{"timestamp":" 946782720335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782722950","data":{"timestamp":" 946782722950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782725026","data":{"timestamp":" 946782725026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782728187","data":{"timestamp":" 946782728187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782730033","data":{"timestamp":" 946782730033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782733669","data":{"timestamp":" 946782733669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782735673","data":{"timestamp":" 946782735672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782738077","data":{"timestamp":" 946782738077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782740285","data":{"timestamp":" 946782740285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782742737","data":{"timestamp":" 946782742737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782744941","data":{"timestamp":" 946782744941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782745447","data":{"timestamp":" 946782745447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782746232","data":{"timestamp":" 946782746231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782747116","data":{"timestamp":" 946782747116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782747297","data":{"timestamp":" 946782747296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782747811","data":{"timestamp":" 946782747810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782750910","data":{"timestamp":" 946782750909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782753271","data":{"timestamp":" 946782753271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782755573","data":{"timestamp":" 946782755572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782758650","data":{"timestamp":" 946782758650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782760411","data":{"timestamp":" 946782760410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782763346","data":{"timestamp":" 946782763346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782765215","data":{"timestamp":" 946782765215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782765709","data":{"timestamp":" 946782765709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782766789","data":{"timestamp":" 946782766788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782767413","data":{"timestamp":" 946782767412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" MWELEKEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782768037","data":{"timestamp":" 946782768036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782768526","data":{"timestamp":" 946782768526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782769470","data":{"timestamp":" 946782769469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" KUEPUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782769972","data":{"timestamp":" 946782769972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" KULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782770140","data":{"timestamp":" 946782770140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782770621","data":{"timestamp":" 946782770621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782773555","data":{"timestamp":" 946782773554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782776194","data":{"timestamp":" 946782776194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782778634","data":{"timestamp":" 946782778634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782780985","data":{"timestamp":" 946782780985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782782946","data":{"timestamp":" 946782782946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782786945","data":{"timestamp":" 946782786945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782789399","data":{"timestamp":" 946782789398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782791230","data":{"timestamp":" 946782791230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782793187","data":{"timestamp":" 946782793186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782794968","data":{"timestamp":" 946782794968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782796990","data":{"timestamp":" 946782796989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782797242","data":{"timestamp":" 946782797242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782804352","data":{"timestamp":" 946782804351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" bf245fcc-902b-4f85-82b8-51295a1dc23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782815878","data":{"timestamp":" 946782815878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 15851ce3-4b22-4b3b-b5b1-0dde180e14b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_jara-goli-zeti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782816356","data":{"timestamp":" 946782816356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 15851ce3-4b22-4b3b-b5b1-0dde180e14b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_jara-goli-zeti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782824846","data":{"timestamp":" 946782824845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 15851ce3-4b22-4b3b-b5b1-0dde180e14b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_jara-goli-zeti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782830087","data":{"timestamp":" 946782830086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 15851ce3-4b22-4b3b-b5b1-0dde180e14b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_jara-goli-zeti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782843636","data":{"timestamp":" 946782843636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782844360","data":{"timestamp":" 946782844360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782844592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782844592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782845285","data":{"timestamp":" 946782845285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782846259","data":{"timestamp":" 946782846259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782847043","data":{"timestamp":" 946782847043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782847327","data":{"timestamp":" 946782847327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782848340","data":{"timestamp":" 946782848340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782851512","data":{"timestamp":" 946782851511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782855482","data":{"timestamp":" 946782855482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782857712","data":{"timestamp":" 946782857712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782862144","data":{"timestamp":" 946782862144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782865198","data":{"timestamp":" 946782865198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782867881","data":{"timestamp":" 946782867880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782869633","data":{"timestamp":" 946782869632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782873028","data":{"timestamp":" 946782873028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782875096","data":{"timestamp":" 946782875096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782876086","data":{"timestamp":" 946782876085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782876871","data":{"timestamp":" 946782876870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782877381","data":{"timestamp":" 946782877381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782878305","data":{"timestamp":" 946782878305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782878941","data":{"timestamp":" 946782878940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782879641","data":{"timestamp":" 946782879639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782880468","data":{"timestamp":" 946782880468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782886013","data":{"timestamp":" 946782886013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782888622","data":{"timestamp":" 946782888622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782891224","data":{"timestamp":" 946782891224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782895357","data":{"timestamp":" 946782895357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782899111","data":{"timestamp":" 946782899111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782902174","data":{"timestamp":" 946782902174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782905374","data":{"timestamp":" 946782905374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782911068","data":{"timestamp":" 946782911068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782912799","data":{"timestamp":" 946782912799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782913203","data":{"timestamp":" 946782913202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782913966","data":{"timestamp":" 946782913965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782915153","data":{"timestamp":" 946782915153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782915590","data":{"timestamp":" 946782915589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782916651","data":{"timestamp":" 946782916649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782919997","data":{"timestamp":" 946782919997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782921706","data":{"timestamp":" 946782921706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782924253","data":{"timestamp":" 946782924252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782928177","data":{"timestamp":" 946782928177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782930799","data":{"timestamp":" 946782930799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782933396","data":{"timestamp":" 946782933396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782935919","data":{"timestamp":" 946782935918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782936753","data":{"timestamp":" 946782936753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782937893","data":{"timestamp":" 946782937892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782947740","data":{"timestamp":" 946782947739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782949835","data":{"timestamp":" 946782949835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782951866","data":{"timestamp":" 946782951866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782953815","data":{"timestamp":" 946782953815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782954144","data":{"timestamp":" 946782954144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782954864","data":{"timestamp":" 946782954864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782956021","data":{"timestamp":" 946782956021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782956241","data":{"timestamp":" 946782956241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782956463","data":{"timestamp":" 946782956463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782957346","data":{"timestamp":" 946782957345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782962914","data":{"timestamp":" 946782962914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782964848","data":{"timestamp":" 946782964848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782967035","data":{"timestamp":" 946782967034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782970635","data":{"timestamp":" 946782970635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782975243","data":{"timestamp":" 946782975243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782977596","data":{"timestamp":" 946782977596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782980955","data":{"timestamp":" 946782980954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782982771","data":{"timestamp":" 946782982770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782983660","data":{"timestamp":" 946782983660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782994279","data":{"timestamp":" 946782994279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782997715","data":{"timestamp":" 946782997715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782999909","data":{"timestamp":" 946782999909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783000916","data":{"timestamp":" 946783000915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783001697","data":{"timestamp":" 946783001697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783002289","data":{"timestamp":" 946783002289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783003715","data":{"timestamp":" 946783003714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" ANAPOITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783004743","data":{"timestamp":" 946783004743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783005133","data":{"timestamp":" 946783005133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783005400","data":{"timestamp":" 946783005400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783005531","data":{"timestamp":" 946783005531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783006925","data":{"timestamp":" 946783006925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783008121","data":{"timestamp":" 946783008120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783009265","data":{"timestamp":" 946783009265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783010189","data":{"timestamp":" 946783010189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783013323","data":{"timestamp":" 946783013322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783015541","data":{"timestamp":" 946783015541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783017567","data":{"timestamp":" 946783017567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783019485","data":{"timestamp":" 946783019485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783021790","data":{"timestamp":" 946783021790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783024107","data":{"timestamp":" 946783024107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783026241","data":{"timestamp":" 946783026241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783028945","data":{"timestamp":" 946783028945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783030976","data":{"timestamp":" 946783030976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783032859","data":{"timestamp":" 946783032859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783035008","data":{"timestamp":" 946783035008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783037908","data":{"timestamp":" 946783037908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783041371","data":{"timestamp":" 946783041371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783043097","data":{"timestamp":" 946783043097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783043927","data":{"timestamp":" 946783043927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783044411","data":{"timestamp":" 946783044410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783045116","data":{"timestamp":" 946783045116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783045869","data":{"timestamp":" 946783045868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783046929","data":{"timestamp":" 946783046928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783048070","data":{"timestamp":" 946783048069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783048935","data":{"timestamp":" 946783048935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783049070","data":{"timestamp":" 946783049070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783049880","data":{"timestamp":" 946783049879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783050487","data":{"timestamp":" 946783050487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783051138","data":{"timestamp":" 946783051137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783052851","data":{"timestamp":" 946783052850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" HUNGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783053486","data":{"timestamp":" 946783053485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783054240","data":{"timestamp":" 946783054240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783055475","data":{"timestamp":" 946783055475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783056759","data":{"timestamp":" 946783056759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783059360","data":{"timestamp":" 946783059360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783061994","data":{"timestamp":" 946783061994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783063694","data":{"timestamp":" 946783063694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783065999","data":{"timestamp":" 946783065999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783068159","data":{"timestamp":" 946783068159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783069982","data":{"timestamp":" 946783069982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783072178","data":{"timestamp":" 946783072178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783076125","data":{"timestamp":" 946783076125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783077819","data":{"timestamp":" 946783077818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783080724","data":{"timestamp":" 946783080724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783083072","data":{"timestamp":" 946783083072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783085004","data":{"timestamp":" 946783085003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783087827","data":{"timestamp":" 946783087827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783089702","data":{"timestamp":" 946783089701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783091508","data":{"timestamp":" 946783091508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783093930","data":{"timestamp":" 946783093929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783096840","data":{"timestamp":" 946783096840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783098809","data":{"timestamp":" 946783098809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783100043","data":{"timestamp":" 946783100043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" HAWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783100897","data":{"timestamp":" 946783100897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783104099","data":{"timestamp":" 946783104099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783107048","data":{"timestamp":" 946783107048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783109988","data":{"timestamp":" 946783109988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783112290","data":{"timestamp":" 946783112290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783112483","data":{"timestamp":" 946783112483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783113019","data":{"timestamp":" 946783113019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783113703","data":{"timestamp":" 946783113703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783114416","data":{"timestamp":" 946783114416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783115220","data":{"timestamp":" 946783115220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783124308","data":{"timestamp":" 946783124308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783126616","data":{"timestamp":" 946783126616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783128464","data":{"timestamp":" 946783128464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783131073","data":{"timestamp":" 946783131072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783133019","data":{"timestamp":" 946783133019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783135309","data":{"timestamp":" 946783135309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783138667","data":{"timestamp":" 946783138667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783139350","data":{"timestamp":" 946783139350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783139764","data":{"timestamp":" 946783139764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783140764","data":{"timestamp":" 946783140764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783141758","data":{"timestamp":" 946783141758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783142631","data":{"timestamp":" 946783142631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783143531","data":{"timestamp":" 946783143529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783144473","data":{"timestamp":" 946783144473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIPUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783145054","data":{"timestamp":" 946783145054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783145605","data":{"timestamp":" 946783145605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783149031","data":{"timestamp":" 946783149031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783151544","data":{"timestamp":" 946783151544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783153737","data":{"timestamp":" 946783153736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783156223","data":{"timestamp":" 946783156223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783158854","data":{"timestamp":" 946783158854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783160848","data":{"timestamp":" 946783160848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783162489","data":{"timestamp":" 946783162488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783164565","data":{"timestamp":" 946783164564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783167420","data":{"timestamp":" 946783167420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783168977","data":{"timestamp":" 946783168977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783171123","data":{"timestamp":" 946783171122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783171426","data":{"timestamp":" 946783171425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783172674","data":{"timestamp":" 946783172674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783174275","data":{"timestamp":" 946783174275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783178469","data":{"timestamp":" 946783178468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783180769","data":{"timestamp":" 946783180769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783183298","data":{"timestamp":" 946783183298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783185446","data":{"timestamp":" 946783185446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783188050","data":{"timestamp":" 946783188049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" UNARINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783188777","data":{"timestamp":" 946783188777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783189865","data":{"timestamp":" 946783189865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783190532","data":{"timestamp":" 946783190532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" KHOVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783191718","data":{"timestamp":" 946783191718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783192710","data":{"timestamp":" 946783192709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783195935","data":{"timestamp":" 946783195935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783197991","data":{"timestamp":" 946783197990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783206728","data":{"timestamp":" 946783206728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783208371","data":{"timestamp":" 946783208370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783213013","data":{"timestamp":" 946783213013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783276523","data":{"timestamp":" 946783276523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783278643","data":{"timestamp":" 946783278643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" ISITOSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783279617","data":{"timestamp":" 946783279617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783280140","data":{"timestamp":" 946783280140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783280473","data":{"timestamp":" 946783280473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783281676","data":{"timestamp":" 946783281676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" MWAFRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783284648","data":{"timestamp":" 946783284648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783286228","data":{"timestamp":" 946783286228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783288060","data":{"timestamp":" 946783288060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783288299","data":{"timestamp":" 946783288299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783288421","data":{"timestamp":" 946783288421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 1a2d4ee9-754f-48c9-9a4c-2d7e8b35cf2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783296868","data":{"timestamp":" 946783296868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783297098","data":{"timestamp":" 946783297097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783298061","data":{"timestamp":" 946783298061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783299334","data":{"timestamp":" 946783299334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783302246","data":{"timestamp":" 946783302246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783303090","data":{"timestamp":" 946783303089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783303403","data":{"timestamp":" 946783303403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783304635","data":{"timestamp":" 946783304635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783308099","data":{"timestamp":" 946783308099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783309083","data":{"timestamp":" 946783309082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783309335","data":{"timestamp":" 946783309335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783310278","data":{"timestamp":" 946783310278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783313102","data":{"timestamp":" 946783313102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783314135","data":{"timestamp":" 946783314135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783314608","data":{"timestamp":" 946783314608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783319129","data":{"timestamp":" 946783319128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783319181","data":{"timestamp":" 946783319181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" 3084a392-6ed3-4650-83b9-bb86945e33f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783333492","data":{"timestamp":" 946783333492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783333715","data":{"timestamp":" 946783333715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783334678","data":{"timestamp":" 946783334678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783335952","data":{"timestamp":" 946783335952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783338806","data":{"timestamp":" 946783338806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783339649","data":{"timestamp":" 946783339648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783339961","data":{"timestamp":" 946783339961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783341208","data":{"timestamp":" 946783341207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783344698","data":{"timestamp":" 946783344697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783345699","data":{"timestamp":" 946783345698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783345957","data":{"timestamp":" 946783345957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783346901","data":{"timestamp":" 946783346901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783349830","data":{"timestamp":" 946783349829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783350862","data":{"timestamp":" 946783350862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783351335","data":{"timestamp":" 946783351335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783352426","data":{"timestamp":" 946783352426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783352507","data":{"timestamp":" 946783352507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.4.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783358910","data":{"timestamp":" 946783358910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" cd959989-185e-4879-9f66-206091d3aa6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783388217","data":{"timestamp":" 946783388217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783401988","data":{"timestamp":" 946783401988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783423480","data":{"timestamp":" 946783423480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783433899","data":{"timestamp":" 946783433899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783435371","data":{"timestamp":" 946783435371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783443984","data":{"timestamp":" 946783443984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783460836","data":{"timestamp":" 946783460836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783478363","data":{"timestamp":" 946783478363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783490162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783490162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783504840","data":{"timestamp":" 946783504840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783513787","data":{"timestamp":" 946783513787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783524239","data":{"timestamp":" 946783524239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8+0"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783532134","data":{"timestamp":" 946783532133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783532441","data":{"timestamp":" 946783532441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783546638","data":{"timestamp":" 946783546637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783553247","data":{"timestamp":" 946783553247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d3c237bc-a8fc-4255-b6b9-48ddc6ec0d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783566565","data":{"timestamp":" 946783566565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d51e60e8-60e8-49cc-b27c-9b1f2b0c591f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783567300","data":{"timestamp":" 946783567300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d51e60e8-60e8-49cc-b27c-9b1f2b0c591f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783567539","data":{"timestamp":" 946783567539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d51e60e8-60e8-49cc-b27c-9b1f2b0c591f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783567689","data":{"timestamp":" 946783567689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d51e60e8-60e8-49cc-b27c-9b1f2b0c591f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783567762","data":{"timestamp":" 946783567762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d51e60e8-60e8-49cc-b27c-9b1f2b0c591f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783576460","data":{"timestamp":" 946783576460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783576692","data":{"timestamp":" 946783576692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783577677","data":{"timestamp":" 946783577675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783578968","data":{"timestamp":" 946783578967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783581916","data":{"timestamp":" 946783581916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783582760","data":{"timestamp":" 946783582760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783583073","data":{"timestamp":" 946783583073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783584307","data":{"timestamp":" 946783584306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783587795","data":{"timestamp":" 946783587795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783588778","data":{"timestamp":" 946783588778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783589031","data":{"timestamp":" 946783589031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783589974","data":{"timestamp":" 946783589974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783591064","data":{"timestamp":" 946783591063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" afabe558-c626-4861-a53c-fba1aec61087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783734369","data":{"timestamp":" 946783734369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783734592","data":{"timestamp":" 946783734592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783735555","data":{"timestamp":" 946783735554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783736828","data":{"timestamp":" 946783736828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783739689","data":{"timestamp":" 946783739689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783740531","data":{"timestamp":" 946783740531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783740844","data":{"timestamp":" 946783740844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783742077","data":{"timestamp":" 946783742077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783745575","data":{"timestamp":" 946783745575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783746559","data":{"timestamp":" 946783746558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783746812","data":{"timestamp":" 946783746812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783747755","data":{"timestamp":" 946783747755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783750643","data":{"timestamp":" 946783750643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783751687","data":{"timestamp":" 946783751687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783752161","data":{"timestamp":" 946783752161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783756663","data":{"timestamp":" 946783756662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783756740","data":{"timestamp":" 946783756740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_054700"," gameId":" d7874e6f-0d66-4c8b-a8c2-2c4cd6934ba5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}